

# EMANOIL ORIANA ELENA

### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

ADDRESS: Bucharest, Romania

PHONE: +40732 713 030

EMAIL: oriana.emanoil@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO: www.oriana.dev

github.com/Jinxulete



live:.cid.9bf1d679840d09de



in/oriana-elena-emanoil-cosma-338487111

#### **EDUCATION**

## The Faculty of Philosophy

University of Bucharest 2011 - 2015

## **Fashion Design**

"Nicolae Tonitza" Fine Arts High School Bucharest 2007 - 2011

#### INTRODUCTION

I am a Front-end developer in love with programming and passionate about creating an amazing user-experience. I have a strong knowledge of the inner workings of the web and the ability to bring websites to life from a mock-up to a fully functional web app.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Front-end Developer, QA Tester & Critical Support Administrator at *Class It Oursourcing*

03/2019-10/2023

Developing and designing webpages maintaining height performance and adaptive modules.

Write clean, well structured maintainable code that conforms with accepted standards and make sure that it is practical and aesthetic at the same time. Manual & automatic Testing Websites and IOS Applications, using Postman & Selenium. Writing testing scenarios and documentations. Monitoring, backup administration(Veeam), configuration, introduction of equipment for Windows and Linux servers. Technologies used:

PHP, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Visual Studio, CSS3, GIT, HTML5, Bootstrap, Angularjs, ReactJS, Postman, Selenium;

# QA Testing at PayScout

06/2017-12/2019

Testing credit cards, using Selenium to make manual testing into automatic. Technologies used: Selenium and Postman;

#### Game Tester at Ea Games

02/2016-04/2017

Testing video games on ps3, ps4, XP0, pc and report the bugs.

#### COOL THINGS I MADE

<u>sigurantapenet</u> Presentation website build with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and

React.

#### SKILLS

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

React

Postman

Selenium









